<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  - SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
  - SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2020-2021 Carl Schwan <carlschwan@kde.org>
 -->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.tokodon</id>
  <provides>
    <binary>tokodon</binary>
  </provides>
  <name>Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">توكودون</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">टोकोडोन</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਟੂਕੂਡੂਨ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="sa">तोकोदोन्</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="sq">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Tokodon</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Tokodon</name>
  <summary>Browse the Fediverse</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">تصفح فيديفيرس</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Navegueu pel Fedivers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Navegueu per Fedivers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Browse the Fediverse</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Foliumi la Fediverson</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Explorar el Fediverso</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Arakatu Fedibertsioa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Selaa fediversumia</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Naviguer dans le Fediverse</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Explore o Fediverso</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">מסע בפדיברס</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">फेडिवर्स ब्राउज़ करें</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">A Fediverse böngészése</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Naviga il Fediverso</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">Fediverse-ის დათვალიერება</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">연합우주 탐색하기</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Pārlūkojiet „Fediverse“</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">In de Fediverse bladeren</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Bla gjennom Allheimen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Przejrzyj Fediverse</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Navegue no Fediverse</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Просмотр Fediverse</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sa">Fediverse ब्राउज् कुर्वन्तु</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Brskaj po fediversu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sq">Shfletoni Fediversin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Bläddra på Fediverse</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Fediverse’i Tarayın</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Навігація Fediverse</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">浏览Fediverse</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">瀏覽聯邦宇宙</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Tokodon is a Mastodon client. It allows you to interact with the Fediverse community.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">توكودون هو عميل ماستودون. يسمح لك بالتفاعل مع مجتمع فيديفيرس.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Tokodon és un client de Mastodon. Permet que interactueu amb la comunitat Fedivers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Tokodon és un client de Mastodon. Permet que interactueu amb la comunitat Fedivers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Tokodon ist ein Mastodon-Client. Er ermöglicht Ihnen die Interaktion mit der Fediverse-Gemeinschaft.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Tokodon is a Mastodon client. It allows you to interact with the Fediverse community.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Tokodon estas Mastodon-kliento. Ĝi permesas vin interagi kun la komunumo Fediverse.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Tokodon es un cliente de Mastodon. Le permite interactuar con la comunidad del Fediverso.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">«Tokodon» «Mastodon» bezero bat da. «Fedibertso» komunitatearekin harremanak izateko aukera ematen du.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Tokodon on Mastodon-asiakas, jolla voit olla vuorovaikutuksessa Fediverse-yhteisöön.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Tokodon est un client Mastodon. Il vous permet d'interagir avec la communauté Fediverse.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Tokodon é un cliente para Mastodon. Permíteche relacionarte coa comunidade do Fediverso.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">Tokodon הוא לקוח Mastodon. הוא מאפשר לתקשר בקהילת הפדיברס.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">टोकोडॉन एक मैस्टोडॉन क्लाइंट है। यह आपको फेडिवर्स समुदाय के साथ बातचीत करने की अनुमति देता है।</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Tokodon egy Mastodon kliens. Lehetővé teszi a kapcsolattartást a Fediverse közösséggel.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Tokodon adalah klien Mastodon. Ini memungkinkan kamu untuk berinteraksi dengan komunitas Fediverse.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Tokodon er Mastodon-forrit. Það gerir þér kleift að eiga samskipti við þá sem eru á Fediverse-samfélagsnetum.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Tokodon è un cliente Mastodon. Ti consente di interagire con la comunità del Fediverso.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Tokodon -ი Mastodon -ის კლიენტია. ის საშუალებას გაძლევთ Fediverse -ის საზოგადოებასთან იკონტაქტოთ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Tokodon은 마스토돈 클라이언트입니다. Fediverse 커뮤니티를 사용할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">„Tokodon“ ir „Mastodon“ klients. Tas ļauj mijiedarboties ar „Fediverse“ kopienu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Tokodon is een Mastodon-client. Het biedt u interactie met de Fediverse gemeenschap.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Tokodon er ein Mastodon-klient som lèt deg kommunisera med fellesskapet på Allheimen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਟੂਕੂਡੂਨ ਮਸਟੂਡੂਨ ਕਲਾਈਂਟ ਹੈ। ਇਹ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਫ਼ੇਡਾਈਵਰਸ ਸਮਾਜ ਨਾਲ ਸੰਪਰਕ ਵਿੱਚ ਰਹਿਣ ਲਈ ਮਦਦਗਾਰ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Tokodon to program do Mastodona. Umożliwia działanie w społeczności Fediverse.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Tokodon é um cliente de Mastodon. Permite-lhe interagir com a comunidade Fediverse.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Tokodon é um cliente Mastodon. Ele permite a você interagir com a comunidade do Fediverse.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Tokodon — клиент Mastodon. Программа позволяет взаимодействовать с сообществом Fediverse.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">टोकोडोन् मस्टोडन् ग्राहकः अस्ति । एतेन भवन्तः Fediverse समुदायेन सह अन्तरक्रियां कर्तुं शक्नुवन्ति ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Tokodon je odjemalec za Mastodon. Omogoča interakcijo s skupnostjo Fediverse.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sq">Tokodon është një klient Mastodon-i. Ju lejon të ndërveproni me bashkësinë Fediverse.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Tokodon är en Mastodon-klient. Den låter dig interagera med Fediverse-gemenskapen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Tokodon, bir Mastodon istemcisidir. Fediverse topluluğu ile etkileşmenize izin verir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Tokodon — клієнт Mastodon. За його допомогою ви можете спілкуватися із учасниками спільноти Fediverse.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">Tokodon 是一个 Mastodon 客户端。它允许您与 Fediverse 社区进行交互。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Tokodon 是一個 Mastodon 用戶端。它讓您與聯邦宇宙社群進行互動。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/tokodon/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=Tokodon</url>
  <url type="donation">https://kde.org/donate/?app=tokodon</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://invent.kde.org/network/tokodon/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://community.kde.org/Get_Involved/translation</url>
  <url type="contact">https://discuss.kde.org/tag/tokodon</url>
  <url type="contribute">https://community.kde.org/Get_Involved</url>
  <categories>
    <category>Network</category>
  </categories>
  <developer id="kde.org">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#cdecfc</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#17a3ea</color>
  </branding>
  <custom>
    <value key="KDE::matrix">#tokodon:kde.org</value>
    <value key="KDE::mastodon">https://kde.social/@tokodon</value>
  </custom>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.tokodon.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/tokodon/tokodon-desktop.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/tokodon/tokodon-notifications.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="25.12.2" date="2026-02-05"/>
    <release version="25.12.1" date="2026-01-08"/>
    <release version="25.12.0" date="2025-12-11"/>
    <release version="25.08.3" date="2025-11-06"/>
    <release version="25.08.2" date="2025-10-09"/>
    <release version="25.08.1" date="2025-09-11"/>
    <release version="25.08.0" date="2025-08-14"/>
    <release version="25.04.3" date="2025-07-03"/>
    <release version="25.04.2" date="2025-06-05"/>
    <release version="25.04.1" date="2025-05-08"/>
    <release version="25.04.0" date="2025-04-17"/>
    <release version="24.12.3" date="2025-03-06"/>
    <release version="24.12.2" date="2025-02-06"/>
    <release version="24.12.1" date="2025-01-09"/>
    <release version="24.12.0" date="2024-12-12"/>
    <release version="24.08.3" date="2024-11-07"/>
    <release version="24.08.2" date="2024-10-10"/>
    <release version="24.08.1" date="2024-09-12"/>
    <release version="24.08.0" date="2024-08-22"/>
    <release version="24.05.2" date="2024-07-04"/>
    <release version="24.05.1" date="2024-06-13"/>
    <release version="24.05.0" date="2024-05-23"/>
    <release version="24.02.2" date="2024-04-11"/>
    <release version="24.02.1" date="2024-03-21"/>
    <release version="24.02.0" date="2024-02-28">
      <url>https://kde.org/announcements/megarelease/6/#tokodon</url>
      <description>
        <p>In this release, writing new posts is even easier. You can set the focal points that your followers will see when viewing your post in their timeline. Images can be copy-pasted or dropped in the composer. When discarding your draft, a configuration popup will prevent you from deleting your post by mistake.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">في هذا الإصدار، أصبحت كتابة المنشورات الجديدة أسهل. يمكنك ضبط نقاط التركيز التي سيراها متابعوك عند عرض منشورك في الخط الزمني الخاص بهم. يمكن نسخ ولصق الصور أو إسقاطها في الملحن. عند تجاهل مسودتك، ستمنعك منبثقة الضبط من حذف منشورك عن طريق الخطأ.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">En aquesta versió, és encara més fàcil escriure publicacions noves. Podeu establir els punts focals que veuran els vostres seguidors en visualitzar la publicació en la seva línia de temps. Les imatges es poden copiar o deixar anar a l'editor. En descartar un esborrany, una finestra emergent de configuració evitarà que suprimiu la publicació per error.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">En esta versió, és encara més fàcil escriure publicacions noves. Podeu establir els punts focals que veuran els vostres seguidors en visualitzar la publicació en la seua línia de temps. Les imatges es poden copiar o deixar anar a l'editor. En descartar un esborrany, una finestra emergent de configuració evitarà que suprimiu la publicació per error.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">ამ ვერსიაში ახალი პოსტების წერა კიდევ უფრო გამარტივდა. თქვენ შეგიძლიათ მიუთითოთ ფოკუსის წერტილები, რომლებსაც თქვენი მიმდევრები ქრონოლოგიაში პოსტის დათვალიერებისას დაინახავენ. სურათების რედაქტორში ჩასმა კოპირებით ან უბრალოდ გადმოთრევითაცაა შესაძლებელი. შავი ვერსიის გაუქმებისას კონფიგურაციის მხტუნარა ფანჯარა პოსტის შემთხვევით წაშლისგან დაგაზღვევთ.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Nesta versão, escrever novas publicações ficou ainda mais fácil. Você pode definir os pontos focais que seus seguidores verão ao visualizar sua publicação na linha do tempo deles. As imagens podem ser copiadas e coladas ou arrastadas e soltas no editor. Ao descartar seu rascunho, uma janela pop-up de configuração impedirá que você exclua sua publicação por engano.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">В этой версии упрощено создание новых публикаций. Можно задать точки фокусировки, которые будут видны подписчикам в ленте. Изображения можно вставлять в редактор копированием или перетаскиванием. При отмене черновика появляется окно настройки, чтобы избежать случайного удаления публикации.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">V tej izdaji je pisanje novih objav še lažje. Nastavite lahko osrednje točke, ki jih bodo vaši sledilci videli, ko si bodo ogledovali vašo objavo na svoji časovnici. Slike lahko kopirate in prilepite ali spustite v sestavljalnik. Ko zavržete osnutek, vam bo pojavno okno s konfiguracijo preprečilo, da bi po pomoti izbrisali objavo.</p>
        <p>We give you more control over what you see in Mastodon. You can hide boosts and replies in your main timeline. Reporting and muting accounts is now more accessible, with these actions directly available from the timeline. You can also leave comments when your report an offending account.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">نمنحك تحكما أكبر فيما تراه في ماستودون. يمكنك إخفاء التعزيزات والردود في الخط الزمني الرئيسي. أصبح الإبلاغ عن الحسابات وكتمها متاحا أكثر، حيث تتوفر هذه الإجراءات مباشرة من الخط الزمني. يمكنك أيضا ترك تعليقات عند الإبلاغ عن حساب مسيء.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">Us donem més control sobre què veieu a Mastodon. Podeu amagar impulsos i respostes en la vostra línia de temps principal. Informar o silenciar comptes ara és més accessible, amb aquestes accions directament disponibles des de la línia de temps. També podeu deixar comentaris quan informeu d'un compte ofensiu.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vos donem més control sobre què veeu a Mastodon. Podeu amagar impulsos i respostes en la vostra línia de temps principal. Informar o silenciar comptes ara és més accessible, amb estes accions directament disponibles des de la línia de temps. També podeu deixar comentaris quan informeu d'un compte ofensiu.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">ჩვენ Mastodon-ში ნანახ შინაარსზე მეტ კონტროლს გაძლევთ. თქვენ შეგიძლიათ ძირითად ქრონოლოგიაში გაზიარებები და პასუხები დამალოთ. ანგარიშების დარეპორტება და დადუმება ახლა უფრო ხელმისაწვდომია, რადგან ეს მოქმედებები პირდაპირ ქრონოლოგიიდანაა შესაძლებელი. ასევე, შეურაცხმყოფელი ანგარიშის დარეპორტებისას შეგიძლიათ, კომენტარიც დატოვოთ.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Oferecemos mais controle sobre o que você vê no Mastodon. Você pode ocultar impulsionamentos e respostas na sua linha do tempo principal. Denunciar e silenciar contas agora é mais fácil, com essas ações disponíveis diretamente na linha do tempo. Você também pode deixar comentários ao denunciar uma conta ofensiva.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Новая версия позволяет лучше контролировать то, что вы видите в Mastodon: в основной ленте стало возможно скрывать продвижения и ответы. Действия отправления жалобы и блокирования теперь доступны непосредственно из ленты. Кроме того, стало возможным оставлять комментарий к жалобе.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Dajemo vam večji nadzor nad tem, kaj vidite v Mastodonu. Na glavni časovnici lahko skrijete izboljšave in odgovore. Prijava in utišanje računov je zdaj bolj dostopna, saj so ta dejanja na voljo neposredno na časovnici. Ko prijavite račun kršitelja, lahko pustite tudi komentarje.</p>
        <p>We completely redesigned the first launch experience, allowing you to learn more about Mastodon, log in to your existing account, and register an account on a server. Additionally, Tokodon will give you some explanation about errors encountered during login and give you the possibility to try again.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">أُعيد تصميم تجربة التشغيل الأولى بالكامل، مما يتيح لك معرفة المزيد عن ماستودون، والولوج إلى حسابك الحالي، وتسجيل حساب في خادم. بالإضافة إلى ذلك، سيقدم لك توكودون بعض الشرح حول الأخطاء التي صودفت أثناء الولوج ويمنحك إمكانية المحاولة مرة أخرى.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">Hem redissenyat completament la primera experiència de llançament, permetent-vos aprendre més sobre Mastodon, iniciar sessió al vostre compte existent i registrar un compte en un servidor. A més, el Tokodon us donarà una explicació dels errors trobats durant l'inici de sessió i us donarà la possibilitat de tornar-ho a provar.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Hem redissenyat completament la primera experiència de llançament, permetent-vos aprendre més sobre Mastodon, iniciar sessió al vostre compte existent i registrar un compte en un servidor. A més, Tokodon vos donarà una explicació dels errors trobats durant l'inici de sessió i vos donarà la possibilitat de tornar-ho a provar.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">ჩვენ პროგრამის პირველი გაშვების პროცესი სრულად გადავაკეთეთ, რაც საშუალებას გაძლევთ, გაიგოთ მეტი Mastodon-ის შესახებ, შეხვიდეთ თქვენს არსებულ ანგარიშზე და დაარეგისტრიროთ ახალი ანგარიში სერვერზე. გარდა ამისა, Tokodon-ი ავტორიზაციისას წარმოქმნილი შეცდომების შესახებ განმარტებებს მოგაწვდით და ხელახლა ცდის შესაძლებლობას მოგცემთ.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Redesenhamos completamente a experiência de primeiro acesso, permitindo que você aprenda mais sobre o Mastodon, faça login em sua conta existente e registre uma conta em um servidor. Além disso, o Tokodon fornecerá explicações sobre erros encontrados durante o login e lhe dará a possibilidade de tentar novamente.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Диалог первого запуска был полностью переработан, и теперь позволяет больше узнать о Mastodon, войти в свою существующую учётную запись или зарегистрировать новую учётную запись на сервере. Кроме того, Tokodon, в случае возникновения ошибок при входе в систему, предоставит объяснение и предложит повторить попытку.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Popolnoma smo prenovili izkušnjo prvega zagona, ki vam omogoča, da izveste več o Mastodonu, se prijavite v svoj obstoječi račun in registrirate račun na strežniku. Poleg tega vam bo Tokodon podal nekaj pojasnil o napakah, ki so se pojavile med prijavo, in vam dal možnost, da poskusite znova.</p>
        <p>We also redesigned the profile pages. The new profile page also allows filtering posts on a profile by their featured tags.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">أُعيد أيضا تصميم صفحات التشكيلة. تتيح صفحة التشكيلة الجديدة أيضا ترشيح المنشورات في التشكيلة حسب وسومها المميزة.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">També hem redissenyat les pàgines de perfils. La pàgina nova del perfil també permet filtrar les entrades d'un perfil per les seves etiquetes destacades.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">També hem redissenyat les pàgines de perfils. La pàgina nova del perfil també permet filtrar les entrades d'un perfil per les seues etiquetes destacades.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">ჩვენ პროფილის გვერდებიც გადავაკეთეთ. პროფილის ახალი გვერდი ასევე იძლევა პოსტების გაფილტვრის საშუალებას მათი რჩეული ჭდეების მიხედვით.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Também redesenhamos as páginas de perfil. A nova página de perfil permite filtrar as publicações de um perfil pelas suas etiquetas em destaque.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Страница профиля была переработана и теперь позволяет фильтровать сообщения по их тегам.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Prav tako smo preoblikovali strani profilov. Nova stran profila omogoča tudi filtriranje objav v profilu po njihovih predstavljenih oznakah.</p>
        <p>And more:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">والمزيد:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">I més:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">I més:</p>
        <p xml:lang="he">ויש עוד:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">და კიდევ:</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">En meer:</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">E mais:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">И ещё:</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">In več:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Color themes support on Android</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">دعم سمات الألوان على أندرويد</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Implementació de temes de color a l'Android</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Implementació de temes de color a Android</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Compatibilidad con temas de color en Android</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">תמיכה בערכות צבע ב־Android</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">ფერადი თემების მხარდაჭერა Android-ზე</li>
          <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor kleurthema's op Android</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a temas de cores no Android</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка цветовых схем в Android</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Podpora za barvne teme v sistemu Android</li>
          <li>TweetDeck-style cross account actions</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إجراءات عابرة للحسابات بنمط TweetDeck</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Accions de compte creuat a l'estil TweetDeck</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Accions de compte creuat a l'estil TweetDeck</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Acciones entre cuentas al estilo TweetDeck</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">פעולות חוצות חשבונות בסגנון TweetDeck</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">TweetDeck-ის სტილი ანგარიშის ქმედებებში</li>
          <li xml:lang="nl">TweetDeck-stijl cross-account acties</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Ações entre contas no estilo TweetDeck</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Действия между учётными записями в стиле TweetDeck;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Dejanja za več računov v slogu TweetDecka</li>
          <li>System integration of sharing with Tokodon</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">تكامل النظام للمشاركة مع توكودون</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Integració del sistema de compartir amb el Tokodon</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Integració del sistema de compartir amb Tokodon</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Integración de compartición con Tokodon en el sistema</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">שילוב מערכת לשיתוף עם Tokodon</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">Tokodon-თან გაზიარების სისტემაში ინტეგრაცია</li>
          <li xml:lang="nl">Systeemintegratie van delen met Tokodon</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Integração do sistema de compartilhamento com Tokodon</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Интеграция с системой для отправки сообщений через Tokodon;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Sistemska integracija deljenja s Tokodonom</li>
          <li>List support</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">دعم القوائم</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Implementació de llistes</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Implementació de llistes</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Implementación de listas</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">תמיכה ברשימות</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">ჩამონათვლის მხარდაჭერა</li>
          <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor lijsten</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte à listas</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка списков;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Podpora za seznam</li>
          <li>Moderation tool for admins</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">أداة إشراف للمديرين</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Eina de moderació per als administradors</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Eina de moderació per als administradors</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Herramienta de moderación para administradores</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">כלי פיקוח למנהלים</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">მოდერაციის ხელსაწყო ადმინებისთვის</li>
          <li xml:lang="nl">Hulpmiddel voor moderatie voor systeembeheerders</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Ferramentas de moderação para administradores</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Инструменты модерации для администраторов</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Orodje moderiranja za skrbnike</li>
          <li>Visible post edited status</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">حالة المنشور المعدل مرئية</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">L'estat de publicació editada és visible</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'estat de publicació editada és visible</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Estado de publicación editada visible</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">מצב גלוי לכך שרשומה נערכה</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">ხილული პოსტის ჩასწორების სტატუსი</li>
          <li xml:lang="nl">Zichtbare status na bewerking</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Status de publicação editada visível</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Пометка о том, что сообщение было отредактировано</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Vidno stanje urejanja objave</li>
          <li>Granular notification controls</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">عناصر تحكم دقيقة في التنبيهات</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Controls granulars de notificacions</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Controls granulars de notificacions</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Controles de notificación granulares</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">פקדי התראות נקודתיים</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">მარცვლოვანი გაფრთხილების მართვა</li>
          <li xml:lang="nl">Fijn afregelen van meldingen</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Controle de notificação granular</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Точное управление уведомлениями</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Podrobni nadzor nad obvestili</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.08.5" date="2024-02-15"/>
    <release version="23.08.4" date="2023-12-07"/>
    <release version="23.08.3" date="2023-11-09"/>
    <release version="23.08.2" date="2023-10-12"/>
    <release version="23.08.1" date="2023-09-14"/>
    <release version="23.08.0" date="2023-08-24">
      <url>https://kde.org/announcements/gear/23.08.0/#tokodonhttpsappskdeorgtokodon</url>
      <description>
        <p>In this release, Tokodon received a visual overhaul and the timeline is now much smoother.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">في هذا الإصدار، تلقى توكودون تحسينا بصريا وأصبح الخط الزمني الآن أكثر سلاسة بكثير.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">En aquesta versió, el Tokodon ha rebut una revisió visual i la línia de temps ara és molt més suau.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">En esta versió, Tokodon ha rebut una revisió visual i la línia de temps ara és molt més suau.</p>
        <p xml:lang="es">En esta versión, se ha realizado una revisión visual de Tokodon y la línea de tiempo es ahora mucho más fluida.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">ამ გამოცემაში Tokodon-ის ვიზუალური მხარე სრულად განახლდა და ქრონოლოგია ახლა ბევრად უფრო გლუვია.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Nesta versão, o Tokodon recebeu uma reformulação visual e a linha do tempo agora está muito mais fluida.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">В этой версии Tokodon получил обновлённое оформление, а лента новостей стала намного плавнее.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">V tej izdaji je Tokodon prejel vizualno prenovo, časovnica pa je zdaj veliko bolj gladka.</p>
        <p>More importantly, if you run your own Mastodon instance, you can now manage and moderate your instance directly from within Tokodon. Version 23.08 gives you the tools to manage users and list the instances you want to (or not) federate with.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">والأهم من ذلك، إذا كنت تدير نموذج ماستودون الخاص بك، فيمكنك الآن إدارة نموذجك والإشراف عليه مباشرة من داخل توكودون. يمنحك الإصدار 23.08 الأدوات لإدارة المستخدمين وسرد النماذج التي تريد (أو لا تريد) الاتحاد معها.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">I el més important, si gestioneu la vostra pròpia instància de Mastodon, ara podeu gestionar i moderar la instància directament des del Tokodon. La versió 23.08 us ofereix les eines per a gestionar usuaris i llistar les instàncies amb les quals us voleu (o no) federar.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">I el més important, si gestioneu la vostra pròpia instància de Mastodon, ara podeu gestionar i moderar la instància directament des de Tokodon. La versió 23.08 vos oferix les eines per a gestionar usuaris i llistar les instàncies amb les quals vos voleu (o no) federar.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">რაც კიდევ უფრო მნიშვნელოვანია, თუ თქვენ საკუთარ Mastodon გაშვებულ ასლს ფლობთ, მისი მართვა და მოდერაცია ახლა პირდაპირ Tokodon-იდან შეგიძლიათ. 23.08 ვერსია გაძლევთ ინსტრუმენტებს მომხმარებლების სამართავად და იმ ინსტანციების სიის შესადგენად, რომლებთანაც გსურთ (ან არ გსურთ) ფედერაციული კავშირის დამყარება.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">Belangrijker, als u u eigen Mastodon exemplaar draait, dan kunt u nu uw exemplaar beheren en modereren direct vanuit Tokodon. Versie 23.08 geeft u de hulpmiddelen om gebruikers te beheren en een lijst te maken van de exemplaren waarmee u wilt (of niet) een federatie aangaan.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Mais importante ainda, se você administra sua própria instância do Mastodon, agora você pode gerenciar e moderar sua instância diretamente do Tokodon. A versão 23.08 oferece as ferramentas para gerenciar usuários e listar as instâncias com as quais você deseja (ou não) federar.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Важнее то, что теперь можно управлять собственным экземпляром Mastodon и модерировать его непосредственно из Tokodon. В версии 23.08 добавлены инструменты для управления пользователями и составления списка экземпляров, с которыми требуется (или не требуется) взаимодействовать.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Še pomembneje pa je, da če imate lasten pojavek Mastodona, ga lahko zdaj upravljate in moderirate neposredno znotraj Tokodona. Različica 23.08 vam ponuja orodja za upravljanje uporabnikov in seznam pojavkov, s katerimi se želite (ali ne) povezati.</p>
        <p>Other new features let you share posts through other apps, save your access token securely in KWallet, view all blocked and muted accounts, and pin your status to your profile.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">تتيح لك الميزات الجديدة الأخرى مشاركة المنشورات عبر تطبيقات أخرى، وحفظ رمز الوصول الخاص بك بأمان في KWallet، وعرض جميع الحسابات المحظورة والمكتومة، وتثبيت حالتك في تشكيلتك.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">Altres característiques noves us permeten compartir entrades a través d'altres aplicacions, desar el testimoni d'accés de manera segura al KWallet, veure tots els comptes bloquejats i silenciats i fixar el vostre estat al perfil.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Altres característiques noves vos permeten compartir entrades a través d'altres aplicacions, guardar el testimoni d'accés de manera segura a KWallet, veure tots els comptes bloquejats i silenciats i fixar el vostre estat al perfil.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">სხვა ახალი ფუნქციები საშუალებას გაძლევთ გააზიაროთ პოსტები სხვა აპლიკაციების მეშვეობით, უსაფრთხოდ შეინახოთ თქვენი წვდომის ტოკენი KWallet-ში, იხილოთ ყველა დაბლოკილი და დადუმებული ანგარიში და მიამაგროთ თქვენი სტატუსი პროფილზე.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">Andere nieuwe functies laten u berichten delen via andere toepassingen, uw toegangstoken veilig opslaan in KWallet, alle geblokkeerde en gedempte accounts zien en uw status aan uw profiel vastpinnen.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Outros novos recursos permitem que você compartilhe postagens por meio de outros aplicativos, salve seu token de acesso com segurança no KWallet, visualize todas as contas bloqueadas e silenciadas e fixe seu status ao seu perfil.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Добавлена возможность публикации записей через другие приложения, безопасного хранения токена доступа в KWallet, просмотра всех заблокированных и скрытых учётных записей, а также закрепления статуса в профиле.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Druge nove zmožnosti vam omogočajo deljenje objav prek drugih aplikacij, varno shranjevanje žetona za dostop v KWallet, ogled vseh blokiranih in utišanih računov ter pripenjanje stanja v profil.</p>
        <p>It's also possible to browse the trending tags and posts of your instance.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">من الممكن أيضا تصفح الوسوم والمنشورات الرائجة في نموذجك.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">També és possible navegar per les etiquetes i entrades de tendència de la vostra instància.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">També és possible navegar per les etiquetes i entrades de tendència de la vostra instància.</p>
        <p xml:lang="es">También es posible explorar las etiquetas y publicaciones de tendencias de la instancia.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">ასევე შესაძლებელია თქვენი გაშვებული ასლის პოპულარული პოსტებისა და ჭდეების დათვალიერება.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">Het is ook mogelijk in de trending tags en in berichten van uw exemplaar te bladeren.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Também é possível navegar pelas etiquetas e postagens mais populares da sua instância.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Также можно просматривать популярные метки и записи на вашем сервере.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Možno je tudi brskati po trendnih oznakah in objavah vašega pojavka.</p>
        <p>We have also upgraded the multimedia framework, making the video player much more reliable.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">حدثنا أيضا إطار عمل الوسائط المتعددة، مما جعل مشغل الفيديو أكثر موثوقية بكثير.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">També hem actualitzat l'entorn de treball multimèdia, fent que el reproductor de vídeo sigui molt més fiable.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">També hem actualitzat l'entorn de treball multimèdia, fent que el reproductor de vídeo siga molt més fiable.</p>
        <p xml:lang="es">También hemos actualizado la infraestructura multimedia, haciendo que el reproductor de vídeo sea mucho más fiable.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">ჩვენ მულტიმედიის სისტემაც განვაახლეთ, რამაც ვიდეო დამკვრელი ბევრად უფრო საიმედო გახადა.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">We hebben ook het framework voor multimedia opgewaardeerd, waardoor de videospeler veel betrouwbaarder is geworden.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Também atualizamos a estrutura multimídia, tornando o reprodutor de vídeo muito mais confiável.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Также обновлён мультимедийный фреймворк, что значительно повысило надёжность видеоплеера.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Nadgradili smo tudi multimedijski okvir, zaradi česar je video predvajalnik veliko zanesljivejši.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.04.3" date="2023-07-06"/>
    <release version="23.04.2" date="2023-06-08"/>
    <release version="23.04.1" date="2023-05-11"/>
    <release version="23.04.0" date="2023-04-20">
      <url>https://kde.org/announcements/gear/23.04.0/#tokodonhttpsappskdeorgtokodon</url>
      <description>
        <p>With version 23.04, communicating with your fellow Fediverse users is even easier, thanks to new features like the ability to see previous messages when replying and the ability to send polls to your followers. Tokodon's mobile version also features a dedicated search page to streamline the process of finding specific posts.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">مع الإصدار 23.04، أصبح التواصل مع مستخدمي فيديفيرس الزملاء أسهل، بفضل ميزات جديدة مثل القدرة على رؤية الرسائل السابقة عند الرد والقدرة على إرسال استطلاعات الرأي إلى متابعيك. تتميز نسخة توكودون للهواتف أيضا بصفحة بحث مخصصة لتبسيط عملية العثور على منشورات محددة.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">Amb la versió 23.04, comunicar-se amb els vostres companys usuaris del Fedivers és encara més fàcil, gràcies a característiques noves com la capacitat de veure missatges anteriors en respondre i la capacitat d'enviar enquestes als vostres seguidors. La versió mòbil del Tokodon també compta amb una pàgina de cerca dedicada per a simplificar el procés de trobar entrades específiques.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Amb la versió 23.04, comunicar-se amb els vostres companys usuaris de Fedivers és encara més fàcil, gràcies a característiques noves com la capacitat de veure missatges anteriors en respondre i la capacitat d'enviar enquestes als vostres seguidors. La versió mòbil de Tokodon també compta amb una pàgina de busca dedicada per a simplificar el procés de trobar entrades específiques.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">23.04 ვერსიით ფედერაციული ქსელის სხვა მომხმარებლებთან კომუნიკაცია კიდევ უფრო გამარტივდა ისეთი ახალი ფუნქციების წყალობით, როგორიცაა პასუხისას წინა შეტყობინებების ნახვისა და მიმდევრებისთვის გამოკითხვების გაგზავნის შესაძლებლობა. Tokodon-ის მობილურ ვერსიაში ასევე დაემატა ძიების სპეციალური გვერდი კონკრეტული პოსტების პოვნის პროცესის გასამარტივებლად.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">Met versie 23.04 is communiceren met uw medegebruikers van Fediverse zelfs gemakkelijker, dankzij nieuwe functies zoals de mogelijkheid om eerdere berichten te zien bij antwoorden en de mogelijkheid om peilingen te verzenden naar uw volgers. de mobiele versue van Tokodon heeft ook een daaraan gewijde zoekpagina om het proces van zoeken naar specifieke posts te stroomlijnen.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Com a versão 23.04, a comunicação com outros usuários do Fediverse ficou ainda mais fácil, graças a novos recursos como a possibilidade de ver mensagens anteriores ao responder e a possibilidade de enviar enquetes aos seus seguidores. A versão mobile do Tokodon também conta com uma página de busca dedicada para agilizar o processo de encontrar postagens específicas.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">В версии 23.04 общение с другими пользователями Федиверса стало ещё проще благодаря таким новым функциям, как просмотр предыдущих сообщений при ответе и возможность отправлять опросы подписчикам. В мобильной версии Tokodon также появилась отдельная страница поиска для быстрого нахождения конкретных записей.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Z različico 23.04 je komunikacija z drugimi uporabniki Fediverse še lažja, zahvaljujoč novim funkcijam, kot sta možnost ogleda prejšnjih sporočil pri odgovarjanju in možnost pošiljanja anket vašim sledilcem. Mobilna različica Tokodona ima tudi namensko stran za iskanje, ki poenostavi postopek iskanja določenih objav.</p>
        <p>Furthermore, version 23.04 enhances your privacy by allowing you to configure a proxy before logging into your Mastodon account. You can also view a list of follow requests, giving you more control over who you interact with on the Fediverse.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">علاوة على ذلك، يعزز الإصدار 23.04 خصوصيتك من خلال السماح لك بضبط الوكيل قبل الولوج إلى حساب ماستودون الخاص بك. يمكنك أيضا عرض قائمة بطلبات المتابعة، مما يمنحك تحكما أكبر في من تتفاعل معه على فيديفيرس.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">A més, la versió 23.04 millora la vostra privadesa permetent-vos configurar un servidor intermediari abans d'iniciar sessió al vostre compte de Mastodon. També podeu veure una llista de peticions de seguiment, donant-vos més control sobre amb qui interactueu al Fedivers.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">A més, la versió 23.04 millora la vostra privadesa permetent-vos configurar un servidor intermediari abans d'iniciar sessió al vostre compte de Mastodon. També podeu veure una llista de peticions de seguiment, donant-vos més control sobre amb qui interactueu a Fedivers.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">გარდა ამისა, 23.04 ვერსია თქვენს კონფიდენციალურობას აუმჯობესებს, რადგან Mastodon-ის ანგარიშზე შესვლამდე პროქსის კონფიგურაციის საშუალებას გაძლევთ. თქვენ ასევე შეგიძლიათ, იხილოთ გამოწერის მოთხოვნების სია, რაც მეტ კონტროლს გაძლევთ იმაზე, თუ ვისთან გექნებათ ურთიერთობა ფედერაციულ ქსელში.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">Verder verhoogt versie 23.04 uw privacy door u toe te staan een proxy te configureren alvorens u aan te melden bij ue Mastodon account. U kunt ook een lijst van volgverzoeken bekijken, waarmee u meer controle hebt over met wie u interact op de Fediverse.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Além disso, a versão 23.04 aumenta sua privacidade, permitindo que você configure um proxy antes de fazer login na sua conta Mastodon. Você também pode visualizar uma lista de solicitações de acompanhamento, dando a você mais controle sobre com quem você interage no Fediverse.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Кроме того, в версии 23.04 улучшена защита приватности: появилась возможность настройки прокси перед входом в учётную запись Mastodon. Также добавлен просмотр списка запросов на подписку, что даёт больше контроля над тем, с кем вы взаимодействуете в Федивёрсе.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Poleg tega različica 23.04 izboljšuje vašo zasebnost, saj vam omogoča konfiguracijo posrednika, preden se prijavite v svoj račun Mastodon. Ogledate si lahko tudi seznam zahtev za sledenje, kar vam daje večji nadzor nad tem, s kom komunicirate na Fediversu.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.02.0" date="2023-02-17">
      <url>https://carlschwan.eu/2023/02/17/tokodon-23.02-release/</url>
      <description>
        <p>This release improve the post composer, making it possible to add alternative text for screen readers and generally the experience more reliable. Aside from that it is not possible to edit your post, see all your bookmarks and favorite posts and much more.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">يحسن هذا الإصدار ملحن المنشورات، مما يجعل من الممكن إضافة نص بديل لقارئات الشاشة ويجعل التجربة أكثر موثوقية بشكل عام. بصرف النظر عن ذلك، يمكن تحرير منشورك، ورؤية جميع علاماتك المرجعية ومنشوراتك المفضلة وأكثر من ذلك بكثير.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">Aquest llançament millora l'editor de publicacions, permetent afegir text alternatiu per als lectors de pantalla i en general l'experiència és més fiable. A part d'això, no és possible editar la vostra publicació, veure tots els vostres punts i publicacions preferides i molt més.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Este llançament millora l'editor de publicacions, permetent afegir text alternatiu per als lectors de pantalla i en general l'experiència és més fiable. A part d'açò, no és possible editar la vostra publicació, veure tots els vostres punts i publicacions preferides i molt més.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">ამ გამოცემაში გაუმჯობესდა პოსტის რედაქტორი, რაც ეკრანის მკითხველებისთვის ალტერნატიული ტექსტის დამატების საშუალებას იძლევა და მთლიანობაში პროცესს უფრო საიმედოს ხდის. გარდა ამისა, ახლა უკვე შესაძლებელია პოსტების ჩასწორება, სანიშნეებისა და რჩეული პოსტების ნახვა და მრავალი სხვა.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Esta versão aprimora o editor de postagens, possibilitando a adição de texto alternativo para leitores de tela e, de modo geral, tornando a experiência mais confiável. Além disso, não é possível editar suas postagens, visualizar seus favoritos e marcadores, e muito mais.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">В этой версии улучшен редактор сообщений: добавлена возможность указывать альтернативный текст для экранных дикторов, а также повышена общая надёжность. Кроме того, реализовано редактирование сообщений, просмотр закладок и избранных сообщений, а также множество других возможностей.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Ta izdaja izboljšuje sestavljalnik objav, saj omogoča dodajanje alternativnega besedila za bralnike zaslona in na splošno zanesljivejšo izkušnjo. Razen tega ni mogoče urejati objave, si ogledati vseh zaznamkov in priljubljenih objav ter še veliko več.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.01.0" date="2023-01-02">
      <url>https://carlschwan.eu/2023/01/02/tokodon-23.01-release/</url>
      <description>
        <p>This release makes it possible to search with tokodon, handles hashtag, adds a account editor and a conversation view</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">يتيح هذا الإصدار إمكانية البحث باستخدام توكودون، ويتعامل مع الوسوم، ويضيف محررا للحساب وعرضا للمحادثة</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">Aquest llançament permet cercar amb el Tokodon, gestiona les etiquetes, afegeix un editor de comptes i una vista de conversa</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Este llançament permet buscar amb Tokodon, gestiona les etiquetes, afig un editor de comptes i una vista de conversa</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">ამ გამოცემაში Tokodon-ით ძებნა უკვე შესაძლებელია. აპლიკაცია მხარს უჭერს ჰეშთეგებს, ასევე დაემატა ანგარიშის რედაქტორი და საუბრის ხედი</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Esta versão permite pesquisar com o Tokodon, suporta hashtags, adiciona um editor de conta e uma visualização de conversas.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">В этой версии добавлены поиск, поддержка хештегов, редактор учётных записей и просмотр обсуждений.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Ta izdaja omogoča iskanje s tokodonom, obravnava hashtag, dodaja urejevalnik računov in pogled pogovorov</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.11.2" date="2022-12-17">
      <description>
        <p>This release fix some regressions and a packaging issue.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">يصلح هذا الإصدار بعض التراجعات ومشكلة في الحزم.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">Aquest llançament soluciona algunes regressions i un problema d'empaquetatge.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Este llançament soluciona algunes regressions i un problema d'empaquetatge.</p>
        <p xml:lang="es">Esta versión corrige algunas regresiones y un problema de empaquetado.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">ეს ვერსია ასწორებს რამდენიმე რეგრესიისა და შეფუთვის პრობლემას.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Esta versão corrige algumas regressões e um problema de empacotamento.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">В этом выпуске исправлены некоторые регрессии и проблема с упаковкой.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Ta izdaja odpravlja nekatere regresije in težave s pakiranjem.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.11.1" date="2022-12-06">
      <description>
        <p>This release contains a lot of bugfixes (including one for a pretty serious crash). This also improve the look of the reaction buttons and improve the layout of the timeline.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">يحتوي هذا الإصدار على الكثير من إصلاحات الأخطاء (بما في ذلك إصلاح لانهيار خطير للغاية). يحسن هذا أيضا مظهر أزرار التفاعل ويحسن تخطيط الخط الزمني.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">Aquest llançament conté moltes correccions d'errors (inclosa una per a una fallada força greu). Aquest també millora l'aspecte dels botons de reacció i millora la disposició de la línia de temps.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Este llançament conté moltes esmenes d'errors (inclosa una per a una fallada força greu). Este també millora l'aspecte dels botons de reacció i millora la disposició de la línia de temps.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">ეს გამოცემა უამრავ ხარვეზის გასწორებას შეიცავს (მათ შორის ერთ-ერთი საკმაოდ სერიოზულ ავარიულ გათიშვას ეხება). ასევე, გაუმჯობესდა რეაქციის ღილაკების ვიზუალური მხარე და დაიხვეწა ქრონოლოგიის განლაგება.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Esta versão contém diversas correções de bugs (incluindo uma para um problema bastante grave que causava um travamento). Ela também melhora a aparência dos botões de reação e o layout da linha do tempo.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">В этой версии исправлено множество ошибок, включая одну, приводившую к аварийному завершению. Также улучшен внешний вид кнопок реакций и компоновка ленты событий.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Ta izdaja vsebuje veliko popravkov hroščev (vključno z enim za precej resno sesutje). Izboljšan je tudi videz reakcijskih gumbov in postavitev časovnice.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.11" date="2022-11-30">
      <url>https://plasma-mobile.org/2022/11/30/plasma-mobile-gear-22-11/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="22.09" date="2022-09-27">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2022/09/27/plasma-mobile-gear-22-09/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="22.06" date="2022-06-24">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2022/06/28/plasma-mobile-gear-22-06/</url>
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Support Mastodon instances installed in subfolder such as Nextcloud social</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">دعم نماذج ماستودون المثبتة في مجلد فرعي مثل Nextcloud social</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Admet instàncies de Mastodon instal·lades en un subcarpeta com ara Nextcloud social</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Admet instàncies de Mastodon instal·lades en un subcarpeta com ara Nextcloud social</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Admite instancias de Mastodon instaladas en subcarpetas, como Nextcloud social</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">Nexcloud social-ის მაგვარ ქვესაქაღალდეში დაყენებული Mastodon-ის გაშვებული ასლების მხარდაჭერა</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a instâncias do Mastodon instaladas em subpastas, como a pasta social do Nextcloud</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка экземпляров Mastodon, установленных во вложенных папках, например Nextcloud Social;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Podpora za pojavke Mastodon, nameščene v podmapah, kot je Nextcloud social</li>
          <li>Add support for cards</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إضافة دعم للبطاقات</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Afegeix la implementació de targetes</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Afig la implementació de targetes</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">נוספה תמיכה בכרטיסים</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">დაემატა ბარათების მარდაჭერა</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionado suporte à cartões</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлена поддержка карточек;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Doda podporo za kartice</li>
          <li>Support desktop notifications and notifications view</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">دعم تنبيهات سطح المكتب وعرض التنبيهات</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Admet notificacions de l'escriptori i la vista de notificacions</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Admet notificacions de l'escriptori i la vista de notificacions</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Admite notificaciones de escritorio y vista de notificaciones</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">תמיכה בהתראות שולחן עבודה ובתצוגת התראות</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">სამუშაო მაგიდის გაფრთხილებებისა და გაფრთხილებების ხედის მხარდაჭერა</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a notificações na área de trabalho e visualização de notificações</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка уведомлений рабочего стола и просмотра уведомлений;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Podpora za obvestila na namizju in pogled obvestil</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.04" date="2022-04-26">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2022/04/26/plasma-mobile-gear-22-04/</url>
      <description>
        <p>Tokodon profile view received many improvements. It's now possible to interact with other accounts directly from it (subscribe, mute, ban, ...), leave note about an account and all the profile information. The desktop mode was also improved.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">تلقى عرض تشكيلة توكودون العديد من التحسينات. أصبح من الممكن الآن التفاعل مع الحسابات الأخرى مباشرة منه (الاشتراك، الكتم، الحظر، ...)، وترك ملاحظة حول حساب ما وجميع معلومات التشكيلة. حُسن وضع سطح المكتب أيضا.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">La vista de perfils del Tokodon ha rebut moltes millores. Ara és possible interactuar amb altres comptes directament des d'ell (subscriure, silenciar, bandejar...), deixar una nota sobre un compte i tota la informació del perfil. També s'ha millorat el mode d'escriptori.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">La vista de perfils de Tokodon ha rebut moltes millores. Ara és possible interactuar amb altres comptes directament des d'ell (subscriure, silenciar, bandejar…), deixar una nota sobre un compte i tota la informació del perfil. També s'ha millorat el mode d'escriptori.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">Tokodon-ის პროფილის ხედი მნიშვნელოვნად გაუმჯობესდა. ახლა უკვე შესაძლებელია სხვა ანგარიშებთან ურთიერთქმედება პირდაპირ პროფილის გვერდიდან (გამოწერა, დადუმება, დაბლოკვა და სხვ), ანგარიშის შესახებ შენიშვნის დატოვება და პროფილის სრული ინფორმაციის ნახვა. ასევე დაიხვეწა კომპიუტერის ვერსიის რეჟიმიც.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">A visualização de perfil do Tokodon recebeu diversas melhorias. Agora é possível interagir diretamente com outras contas (seguir, silenciar, banir, etc.), deixar comentários sobre uma conta e visualizar todas as informações do perfil. O modo desktop também foi aprimorado.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Вид профиля Tokodon был значительно улучшен. Теперь можно взаимодействовать с другими учётными записями напрямую из него (подписываться, отключать звук, блокировать…), оставлять заметки об учётной записи и просматривать всю информацию профиля. Также был улучшен режим для настольных компьютеров.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Pogled profila Tokodon je bil deležen številnih izboljšav. Zdaj je mogoče neposredno komunicirati z drugimi računi (naročiti se, utišati, prepovedati ...), pustiti sporočilo o računu in vse informacije o profilu. Izboljšan je bil tudi namizni način.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.02" date="2022-02-09">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2022/02/09/plasma-mobile-gear-22-02/</url>
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Do not allow posting empty posts</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">عدم السماح بنشر منشورات فارغة</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">No permet enviar publicacions buides</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">No permet enviar publicacions buides</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">No permitir la publicación de mensajes vacíos</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">ცარიელი პოსტების დაპოსტვის არდაშვება</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Não permitir a publicação de postagens vazias</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Запрещена  публикация пустых записей;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Ne dovoli objavljanja praznih objav</li>
          <li>Do not allow to remove login page from stack</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">عدم السماح بإزالة صفحة الولوج من المكدس</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">No permet eliminar la pàgina d'inici de sessió de la pila</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">No permet eliminar la pàgina d'inici de sessió de la pila</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">No permitir la eliminación de la página de inicio de sesión de la pila</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">לא להרשות להסיר את עמוד הכניסה מהערמה</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">შესვლის გვერდის ნაკრებიდან წაშლის არდაშვება</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Não permitir remover a página de login da pilha</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Запрещено удаление страницы входа из стека;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Ne dovoli odstraniti prijavne strani iz sklada</li>
          <li>Fix removal of the accounts</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إصلاح إزالة الحسابات</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Corregeix l'eliminació dels comptes</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Corregix l'eliminació dels comptes</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Se ha corregido la eliminación de cuentas</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">תוקנה הסרת חשבונות</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">გასწორდა ანგარიშების წაშლა</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção na remoção de contas</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено удаление учётных записей;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Popravi odstranjevanje računov</li>
          <li>Add opt-in option to see detailed post stats</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إضافة خيار اختياري لرؤية إحصائيات المنشور التفصيلية</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Afegeix una opció d'alta voluntària per a veure estadístiques detallades de publicacions</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Afig una opció d'alta voluntària per a veure estadístiques detallades de publicacions</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">დაემატა არასავალდებულო პარამეტრი პოსტის დეტალური სტატისტიკის სანახავად</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionar opção de ativação para visualizar estatísticas detalhadas das postagens</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлена опция для просмотра подробной статистики записей;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Doda možnost ogleda podrobne statistike objav</li>
          <li>Fix uploading files</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إصلاح رفع الملفات</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Corregeix la pujada de fitxers</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Corregix la pujada de fitxers</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Se ha corregido el envío de archivos</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">העלאת קבצים תוקנה</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">გასწორდა ფაილების ატვირთვა</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do envio de arquivos</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлена загрузка файлов;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Popravi prenos datotek tja</li>
          <li>General user interface improvements and bugfixes</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">تحسينات عامة على واجهة المستخدم وإصلاحات للأخطاء</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Millores generals en la interfície d'usuari i correccions d'errors</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Millores generals en la interfície d'usuari i esmenes d'errors</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Mejoras generales de la interfaz de usuario y corrección de fallos</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">שיפור ממשק משתמש כלליים ותיקוני תקלות</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">ზოგადი მომხმარებლის ინტერფეისის გაუმჯობესება და შეცდომების გასწორება</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhorias gerais na interface do usuário e correções de bugs</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшения пользовательского интерфейса и исправления ошибок;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Splošne izboljšave uporabniškega vmesnika in popravki napak</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.12" date="2021-12-07">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2021/12/07/plasma-mobile-gear-21-12/</url>
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New logo for application</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">شعار جديد للتطبيق</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Logotip nou de l'aplicació</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Logotip nou de l'aplicació</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Nuevo logotipo para la aplicación</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">לוגו חדש ליישום</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">ახალი ლოგო აპლიკაციისთვის</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Novo logotipo para o aplicativo</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новый логотип приложения;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Nov logotip za aplikacijo</li>
          <li>Add support for navigation toolbar</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إضافة دعم لشريط أدوات التنقل</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Afegeix la implementació de la barra d'eines de navegació</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Afig la implementació de la barra d'eines de navegació</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">נוספה תמיכה בסרגל כלי ניווט</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">დაემატა ნავიგაციის ხელსაწყოთა პანელის მხარდაჭერა</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionado suporte para barra de navegação</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлена поддержка панели навигации;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Doda podporo za navigacijsko orodno vrstico</li>
          <li>Several bugfixes</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إصلاحات أخطاء عديدة</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Diverses correccions d'errors</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Diverses esmenes d'errors</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Diversas correcciones de errores</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">מגוון תיקוני תקלות</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">გასწორდა რამდენიმე შეცდომა</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Várias correções de bugs</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено несколько ошибок;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Več popravkov hroščev</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.08" date="2021-08-31">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2021/08/31/plasma-mobile-gear-21-08/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="21.07" date="2021-07-20">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2021/07/20/plasma-mobile-gear-21-07/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="21.06" date="2021-06-10">
      <description>
        <p>First beta release of Tokodon, with most basic feature working (timeline, sending posts, replying, adding attachements, viewing images and multi-account support).</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">الإصدار التجريبي الأول من توكودون، مع عمل معظم الميزات الأساسية (الخط الزمني، إرسال المنشورات، الرد، إضافة المرفقات، عرض الصور ودعم الحسابات المتعددة).</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">Primera versió beta del Tokodon, amb la majoria de funcions bàsiques funcionant (línia de temps, enviament de publicacions, resposta, afegir adjunts, visualització d'imatges i admet comptes múltiples).</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Primera versió beta de Tokodon, amb la majoria de funcions bàsiques funcionant (línia de temps, enviament de publicacions, resposta, afegir adjunts, visualització d'imatges i admet comptes múltiples).</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">წარმოგიდგენთ Tokodon-ის პირველ ბეტა გამოცემას, რომელშიც ძირითადი ფუნქციები უკვე მუშაობს. ფუნქცია მოიცავს ქრონოლოგიას, პოსტების გაგზავნას, პასუხების დაბრუნებას, ფაილების მიბმას, სურათების დათვალიერებასა და მრავალი ანგარიშის მხარდაჭერას.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Primeira versão beta do Tokodon, com a maioria das funcionalidades básicas funcionando (linha do tempo, envio de mensagens, respostas, adição de anexos, visualização de imagens e suporte a múltiplas contas).</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Выпущена первая бета-версия Tokodon с реализованными основными функциями: лента, отправка записей, ответы, вложения, просмотр изображений и поддержка нескольких учётных записей.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Prva beta izdaja Tokodona, z večino osnovnih zmožnosti (časovnica, pošiljanje objav, odgovarjanje, dodajanje prilog, ogled slik in podpora za več računov).</p>
        <p>Currently big missing features are the support for polls, videos and notifications.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">الميزات الكبيرة المفقودة حاليا هي دعم استطلاعات الرأي، ومقاطع الفيديو، والتنبيهات.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">Actualment les característiques grans que falten són la implementació d'enquestes, vídeos i notificacions.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Actualment les característiques grans que falten són la implementació d'enquestes, vídeos i notificacions.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">ამჟამად დიდი ნაკლული ფუნქციებია არჩევნების, ვიდეოების და გაფრთხილებების მხარდაჭერა.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Atualmente, as principais funcionalidades ausentes são o suporte para enquetes, vídeos e notificações.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">В настоящее время не поддерживаются опросы, видео и уведомления.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Trenutno pomembne manjkajoče zmožnosti so podpora za ankete, videoposnetke in obvestila.</p>
      </description>
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2021/06/10/plasma-mobile-update-june/</url>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">360</display_length>
  </requires>
</component>
